shopto.net 2019-12-07

# Privacy Statement | ShopTo.net

ShopTo.Net understands the value of your privacy, and will therefore only use the information you give us to process your order and provide a quick and convenient service to you in the future (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and General Data Protection Regulation 2018). We do not sell mailing lists to other companies, or divulge any of your personal details to other companies or individuals. All personal details are stored on an off-line server. Payment processing takes place on our secure server provider.

## What information do we need to process an order?

For us to process your order, we will need to obtain:

  * Name
  * E-mail Address
  * Address
  * Credit Card Number and Expiry Date
  * IP Address
  * Phone Number

## How are your personal details kept secure?

When you type in credit card information onto the ShopTo.Net website our secure **PAYMENT SERVICE PROVIDER** Sagepay ([www.sagepay.com](http://www.sagepay.com/)) ensures all details are encrypted at your browser before they are sent to us. While your order is being processed we store your personal details on our in-house servers. Our database is encrypted and the processing servers are not connected to the internet. The servers are physically secured under lock and key.

## Use of personal information

We use the information you provide for the following purposes: 

  * To send status of your order or enquiry
  * To send newsletters and details of offers and promotions which will be of interest
  * To improve the design and content of the website
  * To perform other general marketing and promotional activities focused on our products and services

## Your Consent

When you register at Shopto you will be submitting information giving us the consent to collect and use this information by Shopto and it's Service Provider (if any), however you will be able to unsubscribe at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Tell us what you want

If there are any features that you would like to see available on this site let us know using the ticket system via the contact centre in your account.

### Our Address

**ShopTo.Net**  
Unit 2, The Western Centre  
Western Road,  
Bracknell,  
Berkshire,  
RG12 1RW  
Tel: +44 (0)1344 404773

## Copyright Information

All content on this site is protected under the UK and international copyright laws. No part of this site may be copied, reproduced, distributed, redistributed, modified displayed or performed without prior written consent by **ShopTo.Net** This site is provided as a shopping resource by ShopTo.Net. The site is provided on an "as is" basis. ShopTo.Net makes no express or implied warranties of any kind relating to the provision of information or service on or by this site. **ShopTo.Net** will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use or misuse of this site or any of the information contained within it. We reserve the right to make changes to this site, disclaimers, and terms and conditions at any time.

**ShopTo.Net** , Unit 2, The Western Centre, Western Road, Bracknell, Berkshire, RG12 1RW

## Klarna Privacy Statement

In order to be able to offer you Klarna's payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain aspects of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.

General information on Klarna can be found [here ](https://www.klarna.com/uk/)

Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in [Klarna's privacy policy ](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy)
